A little intelligence goes a long way.
Johnny English Reborn is a crime, action, comedy film directed by Oliver Parker.
The most prominent heads of state in the world begin gathering for a
conference that could have a major impact on global politics.
When MI-7 receives word that the Chinese premier has become the target of some
high-powered killers, it falls on Johnny English to save the day.
Armed with the latest high-tech weaponry and gadgets that would make even James Bond jealous, the once-disgraced agent uncovers evidence of a massive conspiracy
involving some of the world's most powerful organisations, and vows to redeem his tarnished reputation by stopping the killers before they can strike.
Johnny English, played by Rowan Atkinson.
Pamela, played by Gillian Anderson.
Ambrose, played by Dominic West.
Kate, played by Rosamund Pike.
Tucker, played by Daniel Kaluuya.
Quartermain, played by Tim McInnerny.
Johnny English Reborn  is a 2011 spy action comedy film directed by Oliver
Parker and written by Hamish McColl from a story by William Davies.
A sequel to Johnny English (2003) and the second instalment in the Johnny English series, it is a British-French-American
venture produced by StudioCanal, Relativity Media and Working Title Films, and distributed by Universal Pictures.
The film stars Rowan Atkinson (reprising his role as the title character) alongside Gillian
Anderson, Dominic West, Rosamund Pike, Daniel Kaluuya and Richard Schiff as new characters.
Much like its predecessor, the film parodies the James Bond film series and clichés of the spy genre
and marks Atkinson and Tim McInnerny's second collaboration after the series Blackadder.
Johnny English Reborn was met with mixed reviews but has
grossed a total of $160 million worldwide.
The film was released in the United Kingdom on 7 October
2011, and topped the country's box office.
It was later released in North America on 21 October 2011.
A sequel to the film, Johnny English Strikes
Again, was released in October 2018.
The film explores themes of mind control, buddhist monk,
cooking, prime minister, secret agent.
The tone is lighthearted.